<products xmlns="http://schema.zmags.com/product_data_1.0"><properties><property display-name="In Stock" identifier="in_stock" value-type="text" /><property display-name="Store ID" identifier="store_id" value-type="text" /><property display-name="Lang ID" identifier="lang_id" value-type="text" /><property display-name="Catalog ID" identifier="catalog_id" value-type="text" /><property display-name="Order ID" identifier="order_id" value-type="text" /><property display-name="Cat Entry ID" identifier="cat_entry_id" value-type="text" /><property display-name="Calculation Usage ID" identifier="calculation_usage_id" value-type="text" /><property display-name="Ingredients" identifier="ingredients" value-type="text" /><property display-name="Patient Information Url" identifier="patient_information_url" value-type="text" /><property display-name="Points Price" identifier="points_price" value-type="integer" /><property display-name="Collect Points" identifier="collect_points" value-type="integer" /><property display-name="Brand Image Url" identifier="brand_image_url" value-type="text" /><property display-name="Description 1" identifier="description_1" value-type="text" /><property display-name="Description 2" identifier="description_2" value-type="text" /><property display-name="Description 3" identifier="description_3" value-type="text" /><property display-name="Description 4" identifier="description_4" value-type="text" /><property display-name="Description 5" identifier="description_5" value-type="text" /><property display-name="Description 6" identifier="description_6" value-type="text" /><property display-name="Sponsored" identifier="sponsored" value-type="text" /><property display-name="Offer" identifier="offer" value-type="text" /><property display-name="Promotion" identifier="promotion" value-type="text" /><property display-name="Old Price" identifier="old_price" value-type="decimal" /><property display-name="Save Money" identifier="save_money" value-type="decimal" /><property display-name="Price Per Size" identifier="price_per_size" value-type="text" /></properties><delete><product_id>1262637</product_id><product_id>7787715</product_id><product_id>7787758</product_id><product_id>7787723</product_id><product_id>7787731</product_id><product_id>7787707</product_id><product_id>1002773</product_id><product_id>1228529</product_id><product_id>1265002</product_id><product_id>1265003</product_id><product_id>1265004</product_id><product_id>1265005</product_id><product_id>1265006</product_id><product_id>1265007</product_id><product_id>1265008</product_id><product_id>1265009</product_id><product_id>1265010</product_id><product_id>1267828</product_id></delete><update><product><rating>0.0</rating><description_1><![CDATA[<div class="pd_HTML"><div class="productEditorialCopy"><p>This versatile and practical new pencil in the Khol &amp; Contour range offers a variety of make-up results.</p><p>Its hypoallergenic, gliding formula outlines the inner and outer rims of the eye and can also be layered all over the eyelid.</p><p></p><p>A bespoke make-up result, comfortable to wear and lasts for up to 16 hours!</p><p>And it’s good for my eyes! The Shadow &amp; Light eye pencil has been tested under ophthalmological control and is suitable for sensitive eyes and contact lens wearers.</p><p>A double-ended eye pencil for a double effect:</p><ul><li> At one end, the lighter shade, highly concentrated with shimmer, illuminates and opens up the eyes, giving them that extra twinkle! </li> <li> At the other end, the darker colour , highly concentrated with pigments sculpts and intensifies the eyes. </li> </ul></div></div>]]></description_1><product_id>1262637</product_id><store_id>10052</store_id><brand>Bourjois</brand><offer>Buy 1 get 2nd half price on selected Bourjois</offer><calculation_usage_id>-1</calculation_usage_id><cat_entry_id>1262637</cat_entry_id><brand_image_url>43662980-f344-11e1-a21f-0800200c9a66/full/02a5de0f10b87d8d85910e4ab0272064a9ccbee2</brand_image_url><normal_image_url>43662980-f344-11e1-a21f-0800200c9a66/full/0bf4ad3894d8e49810457851b60dfdb208d08c03</normal_image_url><in_stock>IN_STOCK</in_stock><lang_id>-1</lang_id><catalog_id>11051</catalog_id><short_description><![CDATA[<div class="productIntroCopy" property="v:description"><div> Bourjois Kohl &amp; Contour Shadow &amp; Light Eye Pencil duo to sculpt &amp; illuminate. This versatile and practical new pencil in the Khol &amp; Contour range offers a variety of make-up results. </div></div>]]></short_description><order_id>.</order_id><name>Bourjois Kohl &amp; Contour Shadow &amp; Light</name></product><product><points_price>549</points_price><product_id>7787715</product_id><color>BRUN &amp; CARAMEL</color><price>5.49</price><master_product_id>1262637</master_product_id><collect_points>20</collect_points><color_image_url>43662980-f344-11e1-a21f-0800200c9a66/full/da8f79e99aa70802427d871e1f586a9ab3274474</color_image_url></product><product><points_price>549</points_price><product_id>7787758</product_id><color>EBENE &amp; ARGEN</color><price>5.49</price><master_product_id>1262637</master_product_id><collect_points>20</collect_points><color_image_url>43662980-f344-11e1-a21f-0800200c9a66/full/ce6edeebd9dae626e3dfb1a7ab11b5e0e56b72a5</color_image_url></product><product><points_price>549</points_price><product_id>7787723</product_id><color>MARINE &amp; DRAGE</color><price>5.49</price><master_product_id>1262637</master_product_id><collect_points>20</collect_points><color_image_url>43662980-f344-11e1-a21f-0800200c9a66/full/6d5e06d1675ec0403d2d5755e29738cf51b07519</color_image_url></product><product><points_price>549</points_price><product_id>7787731</product_id><color>KAKI &amp; VANILE</color><price>5.49</price><master_product_id>1262637</master_product_id><collect_points>20</collect_points><color_image_url>43662980-f344-11e1-a21f-0800200c9a66/full/3c3949147c785df8fb16154d41b63c01f04360fb</color_image_url></product><product><points_price>549</points_price><product_id>7787707</product_id><color>GRIS &amp; PETALE</color><price>5.49</price><master_product_id>1262637</master_product_id><collect_points>20</collect_points><color_image_url>43662980-f344-11e1-a21f-0800200c9a66/full/df03942c8e184f489ae00be52dcc5feee41374b6</color_image_url></product><product><rating>4.62</rating><points_price>899</points_price><store_id>10052</store_id><size>75 G </size><cat_entry_id>1002773</cat_entry_id><ingredients><![CDATA[<p>Glycerin, PEG-8, caprylyl glycol, sodium polyacrylate, carbomer, sodium hydroxide and purified water. Does not contain any preservatives.</p>]]></ingredients><normal_image_url>43662980-f344-11e1-a21f-0800200c9a66/full/4a05c5873062003a6da77a8679e9c036c6215787</normal_image_url><lang_id>-1</lang_id><short_description><![CDATA[<div class="productIntroCopy" property="v:description"><p>ViraSoothe Chickenpox Relief Cooling Gel helps relieve the irritating symptoms of chickenpox.</p></div><h4>Suitable For</h4><p>Suitable from 6 months onwards.</p><p>Always read the label.</p>]]></short_description><offer>Our first ever 3 for 2 Mix &amp; Match across healthcare - cheapest free. Exclusions apply
</offer><price>8.99</price><calculation_usage_id>-1</calculation_usage_id><in_stock>IN_STOCK</in_stock><name>ViraSoothe Chickenpox Relief Cooling Gel - 75g</name><description_1><![CDATA[<div class="pd_HTML"><div class="productEditorialCopy"><p>ViraSoothe Chickenpox Relief Cooling Gel helps relieve the irritating symptoms of chickenpox.</p><p>The red spots and blisters associated with chickenpox can often become itchy, inflamed and infected with bacteria. Scratching these areas can spread any infection and can lead to scarring. Virasoothe provides cooling and soothing relief to the affected areas, reducing the urge to scratch.</p><p>It contains OSMO 4, a unique patented technology that has been clinically proven to relieve the irritating symptoms of chickenpox by cooling the skin and thereby relieving itching. By protecting the skin's environment it allows the skin to heal naturally which can help reduce long-term scarring.</p></div></div><div class="pd_HTML"><div id="usageInstructions"><h4>How to Use</h4><p><b>How to use ViraSoothe Chickenpox Relief Cooling Gel:</b></p><p><b>Children over 6 months:</b></p><ul><li>Wash and dry hands before use</li><li>Rub the gel into the skin sparingly with a light massaging action.</li><li>Apply two to three times a day or whenever relief is needed.</li></ul><p> </p><p>It can be used all over the face and body.</p><p>Avoid contact with the eyes. For external use only.</p><p><b>Adults, the elderly and children under 6 months: </b>Should only be treated under medical supervision.</p></div></div><div class="pd_HTML"><div id="warnings"><h4>Hazards and Cautions</h4><p>Keep out of the reach and sight of children.</p><p>Avoid contact with the eyes.</p><p>For external use only.</p><p>Please read the enclosed information leaflet carefully before use.</p><p>Talk to your doctor or pharmacist if: you are sensitive to any of the ingredients in Care Virasoothe.</p></div></div>]]></description_1><product_id>1002773</product_id><price_per_size>£11.99 per 100G</price_per_size><order_id>.</order_id><collect_points>32</collect_points><catalog_id>11051</catalog_id></product><product><rating>4.78</rating><points_price>9,999</points_price><store_id>10052</store_id><cat_entry_id>1228529</cat_entry_id><normal_image_url>43662980-f344-11e1-a21f-0800200c9a66/full/d6be1aae04bc17ebf909639af76c8f90bd4e4b77</normal_image_url><lang_id>-1</lang_id><short_description><![CDATA[<div class="productIntroCopy" property="v:description">Giving you plenty to smile about, the <b>Oral-B Professional Care 5000 Triumph Electric Toothbrush</b> <b>with Smart Guide</b> offers the most advanced cleaning technology for unbelievable plaque removal.</div>]]></short_description><price>99.99</price><offer>Save up to 1/2 price on selected Oral B electrical dental</offer><save_money>100.00</save_money><brand>Oral B</brand><old_price>199.99</old_price><calculation_usage_id>-1</calculation_usage_id><in_stock>IN_STOCK</in_stock><brand_image_url>43662980-f344-11e1-a21f-0800200c9a66/full/b55a6226fe2be79e40a32893713dd512dcc34c4b</brand_image_url><name>Oral-B Professional Care triumph electric toothbrush 5000 smart guide</name><description_2><![CDATA[itself provides an audio cue to these as well.</p><p>A change in brushing occurs every 30 seconds to let you know how long you have been brushing, with a final alert at two minutes. The sound also changes to give you a warning signal, letting you know if you are brushing with too much pressure in order to protect your gums.</p><p><b>Brushing Timer: </b>Guides you to brush for two minutes, as recommended by dentists.</p><p><b>Visual Pressure Alert</b>: Smart Guide sets off a visual warning when you are brushing too hard to help you keep control of brushing and protect your gums.</p><p><b>Quadrant Prompt:</b> Prompts you after 30 seconds to change the quadrant, or area, of your mouth, helping you to brush thoroughly across all 4 quadrants of your mouth.</p><p><b>Replace Brush Head Indicator: </b>Dentists recommend that you change your brush head every 3 months, when brushing twice a day for two minutes.<b> Braun Oral-B Triumph 5000 with Smart Guide </b>memorises your absolute brushing time, and tells you when you should replace it, to ensure that you are brushing with a brush head that performs at its best.</p><p></p><b><u>Why use a rechargeable brush?</u></b> <ul><li> Customise your brushing experience with five unique brushing modes. With the push of a button, you can choose the one that’s right for you. </li> <li> Exceptional cleaning of teeth and gums. </li> <li> Gentle stimulation of gums </li> <li> Gentle yet thorough cleaning for sensitive areas </li> <li> Polishing and natural whitening of your teeth to remove stains </li> <li> For that thorough dentist clean feeling </li> <li> Over 75% of dentists now recommend using a rechargeable toothbrush </li> <li> All Oral-B rechargeable toothbrushes are clinically proven to remove more plaque than a manual brush </li> <li> Rechargeable toothbrushes help eliminate human error during brushing, which can lead to more serious gum problems </li> <li> Oral-B 3D technology is clinically proven to remove 2x as much plaque tha]]></description_2><description_3><![CDATA[ a manual brush </li> <li> Oral-B is the number 1 most dentist recommended power toothbrush brand worldwide </li> </ul><p><b><u>Innovative and comfortable design:</u></b></p><p>You’ll enjoy the comfort and look of the<b> Oral B Triumph 5000 toothbrush</b>. A unique, curved handle made of high-tech materials ensures a good grip and comfortable brushing. An easy-to-read digital display communicates key information clearly while the premium overall design ensures you’ll love the way this stylish toothbrush looks in your bathroom.</p><p><b><u>Convenient charging and storage:</u></b></p><p><b>Triumph 5000</b> offers convenience at home – and on the go. The innovative, dishwasher-safe base station provides storage for up to four attachments, plus you have a travel case to store your brush when you’re on the go. A portable smart plug charger with a multi-voltage plug makes travelling with <b>Triumph 5000 </b>easy and the s mart plug charger can be attached to the base station to create a single storage and charging unit.</p><p><b><u>Innovative brush head technology</u></b>:</p><p>Braun Oral-B rechargeable toothbrushes can use any Braun Oral-B brush head (except Pulsonic/Sonic), and the Triumph comes with three innovative brush heads in the pack:</p><p><b><u>Oral B Triumph toothbrush with Smart guide </u></b><u>includes: </u></p><p>• 1 x Braun Oral-B Triumph 5000 rechargeable toothbrush</p><p>• 1 x Smart Guide brushing aid</p><p>• 1 x Charging stand</p><p>• 1 x Floss Action brush head</p><p>• 1 x 3D White brush head</p><p>• 1 x Sensitive brush head</p><p>• 1 x Travel case</p><p>• 1 x Smart plug</p><p>Don't forget to get your <a name="2%20pin%20plug%20adapter" title="2 pin plug adapter" href="http://www.boots.com/en/Boots-Two-Pin-Plug-Adaptor_872939/">2 pin plug adapter</a> so you can charge your toothbrush.</p></div></div>]]></description_3><description_1><![CDATA[<div class="pd_HTML"><div class="productEditorialCopy"><p>This <b>Oral B Triumph 5000 smart guide toothbrush </b>has superior features to its predecessor, with five brushing modes instead of four, an improved base station and a greater selection of toothbrush refills.</p><p>Get a smile you can feel triumphant about. Achieve whiter teeth and healthier gums than you ever thought possible. Experience Oral-B Triumph – a triumph over ordinary brushing.</p><p>During a '<b>Top 5 Electric Toothbrushes</b>' feature in August 2011, a dentist professional worked with Liz, presenter for <b>The Gadget Show</b>, to provide independent insights on each toothbrush's technology and efficacy. Twenty toothbrushes were tested in total, during each round, the toothbrushes that didn't make the grade in terms of features, precision and plaque removal were removed from testing. The <b>Oral B 5000 smart guide electric toothbrush</b> finished <b>number 1, </b>a fantastic testament to the quality of the power brush.</p><p><b><u>Get naturally whiter teeth in just 21 days</u></b></p><p>The experts at Braun Oral-B introduce the <b>Triumph 5000 with Smart Guide</b>, a remote wireless display that tells you when you’re brushing too hard, when to switch sides and how long to brush. It’s clinically proven to help improve your brushing habits within 30 days. And it’s the only brand to be platinum approved by the British Dental Health Foundation.</p><p><b>Oral-B Triumph with Smart Guide</b> is a significant advancement in rechargeable toothbrushes, setting new standards in customisation, feedback mechanisms, and overall brushing design.</p><p><b><u>What is Smart Technology?</u></b></p><p>Smart Technology is built into Braun Oral-B Triumph brush heads and the Smart Guide to provide you with interactive feedback during brushing to help you brush your best every day. The Smart Guide provides visual feedback on the time taken to brush and the pressure you are using to brush your teeth, and the brush head]]></description_1><product_id>1228529</product_id><order_id>.</order_id><collect_points>792</collect_points><catalog_id>10551</catalog_id><promotion>Top 10 most viewed electrical products between 25th August &amp; 31st August 2012</promotion><promotion>Online exclusive - Save £5 on selected electrical beauty products when you enter code E5 at the checkout
</promotion></product><product><rating>5.0</rating><description_1><![CDATA[<div class="pd_HTML"><div class="productEditorialCopy"><p>These Mini Club newborn boys layette short sleeved bodysuits feature an envelope neck and nickel-free poppered gussets for easy changing and dressing. Pack includes one striped bodysuit, two all over print, one with a cute bird character and one with an adorable paw print motif.</p><p>Fabric: 100% Cotton</p><p id="washing_instructions"> <b>Washing Instructions</b></p><p id="washing_instructions"> Warm regular machine wash, Do not bleach, May be tumble dried, Iron on a medium heat, Do not dry clean, Iron on reverse, Wash similar colours together, Keep Away From Fire.</p><p id="washing_instructions"> <img src="/wcsstore/cmsassets/Boots/Library/Icon/Homepage/Brand%20Treatments/Mini%20Club%20NEW%202011/SpringSummer%202012/Sizing%20charts/MC_SizeGuide_SS2012_Collectables/MC_SizeGuide_SS2012_Collectables.jpg" title="Sizing guide" alt="Sizing guide"><img src=""></p><p id="washing_instructions"> <b>Mini Club</b></p><p id="washing_instructions"> Why not explore the other bodysuits and clothing sets from across our Mini Club children’s clothing range? Beautifully designed to suit your little one’s developing needs, Mini Club is our contemporary collection of stylish, comfortable and affordable clothes for children. From baby clothes for newborn and low weight babies, through outfits for toddlers, and clothes for boys and girls up to six-years-old, you’ll find it all in Mini Club. Our range includes everything from leggings and joggers to tops, t-shirts, knitwear, trousers, jeans, socks, tights, coats, jackets, footwear, dresses, skirts, shorts, sleepsuits, rompers, pramsuits, coats, bodysuits, vests and nightwear.</p></div></div>]]></description_1><product_id>1265002</product_id><store_id>10052</store_id><brand>mini club children's clothing</brand><calculation_usage_id>-1</calculation_usage_id><cat_entry_id>1265002</cat_entry_id><brand_image_url>43662980-f344-11e1-a21f-0800200c9a66/full/3a3a96f07ac118778a6870a67e1470d993e408ec</brand_image_url><normal_image_url>43662980-f344-11e1-a21f-0800200c9a66/full/5b7c44f699733bdae709ca7a61837b8f2c32670e</normal_image_url><in_stock>IN_STOCK</in_stock><lang_id>-1</lang_id><catalog_id>11051</catalog_id><short_description><![CDATA[<div class="productIntroCopy" property="v:description"><p>Includes one striped bodysuit, two all over print, one with a bird on and one with a paw print motif.</p><p>Fabric: 100% Cotton</p><p>Washing Instructions: Warm regular machine wash</p><a href="#washing_instructions">View full instructions</a></div>]]></short_description><order_id>.</order_id><name>Mini Club Baby Boys Five Pack Bodysuit</name></product><product><points_price>1000</points_price><product_id>1265003</product_id><price>10.00</price><master_product_id>1265002</master_product_id><size>Up to 3.4kg</size></product><product><points_price>1000</points_price><product_id>1265004</product_id><price>10.00</price><master_product_id>1265002</master_product_id><size>3.4 - 4.5kg</size></product><product><points_price>1000</points_price><product_id>1265005</product_id><price>10.00</price><master_product_id>1265002</master_product_id><size>0 - 3 months</size></product><product><points_price>1000</points_price><product_id>1265006</product_id><price>10.00</price><master_product_id>1265002</master_product_id><size>3 - 6 months</size></product><product><points_price>1000</points_price><product_id>1265007</product_id><price>10.00</price><master_product_id>1265002</master_product_id><size>6 - 9 months</size></product><product><points_price>1000</points_price><product_id>1265008</product_id><price>10.00</price><master_product_id>1265002</master_product_id><size>9 - 12 months</size></product><product><points_price>1000</points_price><product_id>1265009</product_id><price>10.00</price><master_product_id>1265002</master_product_id><size>12 - 18 months</size></product><product><points_price>1000</points_price><product_id>1265010</product_id><price>10.00</price><master_product_id>1265002</master_product_id><size>18 - 24 months</size></product><product><rating>0.0</rating><points_price>429</points_price><store_id>10052</store_id><size>150 ML </size><cat_entry_id>1267828</cat_entry_id><normal_image_url>43662980-f344-11e1-a21f-0800200c9a66/full/28e958a316d5cb4c45b599b24c8bf6d7c9c3af4e</normal_image_url><lang_id>-1</lang_id><short_description><![CDATA[<div class="productIntroCopy" property="v:description">Dove Men+Care Face Wash Sensitive+ has a gentle formula that cleanses thoroughly and is clinically proven to fight skin dryness.</div>]]></short_description><price>4.29</price><brand>Dove</brand><calculation_usage_id>-1</calculation_usage_id><in_stock>IN_STOCK</in_stock><brand_image_url>43662980-f344-11e1-a21f-0800200c9a66/full/cd824b0de4b391a037d513426469fa3f03e36e70</brand_image_url><name>Dove Men+Care Face Wash Sensitive+ 150ml</name><description_1><![CDATA[<div class="pd_HTML"><div class="productEditorialCopy"><p>Dove Men+Care Face Wash Sensitive+ is suitable for daily use. The gentle formula is designed for men's skin:</p><ul><li> Rinse off easily </li> <li> Feel moiturising on skin </li> <li> Be suitable for sensitive skin </li> <li> Dermatologically approved </li> <li> Skin is left clean and cared for </li> </ul></div></div>]]></description_1><product_id>1267828</product_id><price_per_size>£2.86 per 100ML</price_per_size><order_id>.</order_id><collect_points>16</collect_points><catalog_id>11051</catalog_id></product></update></products>